Guide to the Ellington Field research collection, 1917-2009 MS 547
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Personnel Photographs
  - Fagan, Jerry S. (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Falco, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Farley, Stacy G., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Feld, Jerry (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Fenn, Jerald D. (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Fenner, Richard G. (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Fenton, Lewis, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Fernandez, James W. (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Fernandez, Orlando O. (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Files, Kenneth O. (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Fincher, William G. (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Finn, William J. (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Fiorito, Cyde A. (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Fischer, Carl F. (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Fisher, Larry F. (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Fleming, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Fletcher, Wilson L. (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Flinn, William W. (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Floeck, Charles L. (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Folwell, John C. (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - Fontenot, Paul N. (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - Ford, Charles P. (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - Fortune, Donald M. (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Foster, Edward A. (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Foster, Graves N. (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Foster, Weldon T. (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Fowler, Bradley A. (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - Fowler, Coy L. (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - Fowler, Gordon J., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Fowler, Guy B. (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Frank, Henry V. (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Frankson, Wilbur R. (Box 7, Folder 313)
  - Fraser, Lawrence G. (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Frederking, David V. (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Freeman, Billy D. (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Freeman, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Freeman, William D. (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - French, Larry L. (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Fuchs, Carroll G. (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Fugate, George M. (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - Gaedke, Waldo A. (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - Gaffey, Edward J. (Box 7, Folder 323)
  - Gallagher, William J. (Box 7, Folder 324)
  - Gandee, Ronald L. (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - Gandy, Robert E. (Box 7, Folder 326)
  - Ganske, Irwin J. (Box 7, Folder 327)
  - Gantt, Luddie R. (Box 7, Folder 328)
  - Garcia, Luis H. (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - Garcia, Roberto C. (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - Garcia, Ruben R. (Box 7, Folder 331)
  - Garison, Ira G. (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - Garland, Bobby T. (Box 7, Folder 333)
  - Garmany, Richard P. (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - Garrison, Donald E. (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Gates, Milburn J. (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - Gawlik, James D. (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Geldmeier, William L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Gervais, Neil F. (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Getso, Joseph L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - Gibson, David D. (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - Gibson, Virgil L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - Gilliam, Ronald R., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - Glaze, Lawrence B. (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Goad, Edwin L. (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - Godbey, Luther D. (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - Godhelp, Gustave F. (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - Goers, Roger T. (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - Goeters, Joseph E. (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - Golden, James M. (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - Gonzales, Jerome E., II (Box 7, Folder 351)
  - Gonzales, Robert A. (Box 7, Folder 352)
  - Goodner, Gary L. (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - Goodwin, Truman W. (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - Gordon, Edward C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - Gordy, Valrie O. (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - Gore, Alan H. (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - Gore, Edward L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - Gouger, Norman E. (Box 7, Folder 359)
  - Gounaris, George J. (Box 7, Folder 360)
  - Graf, Charles H. (Box 7, Folder 361)
  - Graham, Jordan J. (Box 7, Folder 362)
  - Grant, William J., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 363)
  - Graves, Donald E. (Box 7, Folder 364)
  - Grawey, Anthony F. (Box 7, Folder 365)
  - Green, Dan E. (Box 7, Folder 366)
  - Green, Donald C. (Box 7, Folder 367)
  - Green, Henry O., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 368)
  - Green, Robert S. (Box 7, Folder 369)
  - Greer, Jewell L. (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Grelecki, John R. (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - Grier, Donna B. (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - Griesmyer, Steven C. (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Gross, Howard H. (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Grossholz, Gene P. (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Guerrero, Joe J. (Box 7, Folder 376)
  - Guess, Ottis C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Guettner, David F. (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Guffey, Everette V. (Box 7, Folder 379)
  - Guyon, Donald K. (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Lawson, James M. (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - McCartney, Richard K. (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Montgomery, Norman H. (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Ogden, William J. (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Ordelheide, Meyer F. (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Osteen, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Otte, William K., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Pagan Saez, Nelson (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Pagliuss, Eugene F., Sr. (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Pascal, James B. (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Penney, Billy B. (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Phillips, Charles T. (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Piel, Charles W. (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Potter, Byron R. (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Potter, Ceil (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Present, Stuart M. (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Pullen, William T. (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Raines, William H. (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Ratisseau, Sidney A. (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Reis, Marion L. (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Rodriguez, Joe R. (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Roy, Arda J., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - Santos, Gumercindo, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - Schiebel, Richard H. (Box 7, Folder 404)
  - Schofield, Larimer M. (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - Schoppe, Donald L. (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - Schroeder, Wayne E. (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - Seale, Henry M. (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - Shellshear, Thomas M. (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - Shepherd, Billy R. (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - Sheppard, Alton L. (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - Silguero, Benito (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - Sinclair, Richard D. (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - Skyvara, Richard J. (Box 7, Folder 414)
  - Slaughter, James (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - Smaistrla, Daniel C. (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - Smith, Lindsey T. (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - Smith, Marvin R. (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Sorenson, Nils A. (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - Sparks, James C. (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Staudt, Walter B. (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - St. Cyr, Mark V. (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Stepchinski, Aloysius M. (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - Stockton, Kenneth F.E. (Box 7, Folder 424)
  - Stockwell, William K. (Box 7, Folder 425)
  - Strode, Hubert B., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Taylor, Curtis E. (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - Taylor, Robert H., III (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Taylor, Travis C. (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - Thedford, Robert B. (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - Thomas, James W. (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - Thompson, Frank W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - Thompson, Leroy (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - Tomchesson, Arlan R. (Box 7, Folder 434)
  - Totsky, Herbert P. (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Vick, Joe E. (Box 7, Folder 436)
  - Vick, Joe E. (Box 7, Folder 437)
  - Vincer, Samuel C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Wahrenberger, James E., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 439)
  - Wahrenberger, John W. (Box 7, Folder 440)
  - Walker, Morgan B. (Box 7, Folder 441)
  - Warren, Jimmie L. (Box 7, Folder 442)
  - Waxler, James K., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 443)
  - Westervelt, Lloyd H. (Box 7, Folder 444)
  - Westervelt, Ronald D. (Box 7, Folder 445)
  - Wiatrak, William A. (Box 7, Folder 446)
  - Willard, Charles R. (Box 7, Folder 447)
  - Wind, Erwin L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 448)
  - Woodard, Wendell L. (Box 7, Folder 449)
  - Woodring, Albert L. (Box 7, Folder 450)
  - Woodring, Joseph S. (Box 7, Folder 451)
  - Woods, Paul H. (Box 7, Folder 452)
  - Yerkes, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 453)
  - Young, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 454)
  - Zimmer, Bill E. (Box 7, Folder 455)
  - Zwerneman, Willard W. (Box 7, Folder 456)
  - unidentified (Box 7, Folder 457)
  - Officers Wives Club (Box 7, Folder 458)
  - Officers Wives Club (Box 7, Folder 459)
  - Officers Wives Club (Box 7, Folder 460)
  - Officers Wives Club (Box 7, Folder 461)
  - Officers Wives Club (Box 7, Folder 462)
  - Officers Wives Club - Christmas (Box 7, Folder 463)
  - Officers Wives Club - Cocktails (Box 7, Folder 464)
  - Officers Wives Club – Dinner (Box 7, Folder 465)
  - Officers Wives Club – Dinner (Box 7, Folder 466)
  - Officers Wives Club – Fashion show (Box 7, Folder 467-471)
  - Officers Wives Club – Luncheon (Box 7, Folder 472-476)
  - Col. Mrs. Staudt, Col. Mrs. Rank (Box 7, Folder 477)
  - 147th Airborn best airmen for Nov. 1958 (Box 7, Folder 478)
  - Beck invention – extractor (Box 7, Folder 479)
  - Coupland's tires (Box 7, Folder 480)
- Series III: Books
  - Book, Granville, Tales and Tail Spins from a Flyer's Diary, 1919. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Master's Thesis,A History of Ellington Field, 1918-2003; Eighty-Five Years of Defense in Texas., May, 2003. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Book, From Jennies to Jets; The Story of the 111th Squadron, June 1923-29 June 1973. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Book, Navigation School; Ellington Air Force Base, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Book, Ellington Air Force Base, Aircraft Observer Training, 1955-2956. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Book, Ellington Air Force Base Class 53-16, 3605th Observer Training Group, 1953. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Oversize Items
  - Magazine, "Yank," Middle Pacific Edition, December 28, 1945. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Women Airforce Service Pilots of WWII(WASP), 1943. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Air Show at Ellington Field, Texas, 1 of 2, 1957. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Air Show at Ellington Field, Texas, 2 of 2, 1957. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Addendum
  - Visuals
    - Ellington Field views, WWII (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - NASA instructor station (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Topographic maps (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Gene Autry visit, WWII (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Postcards, WWI (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Postcards, WWII (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Comic postcards, WWII (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Publications
    - Polaris, v.1 no. 4, v. 2 no. 2; 1943-44 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Skylander, 1999-2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Skylander, 2005-10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Skylander, 2012-13 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - History and Rhymes of the Lost Battalion, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ghost Squadron of the Confederate Air Force, 1939-45 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Red Cross Magazine, April 1918 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Houston, Oct. 1945 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - The Flying Prostitute, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Tailspin, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Excerpt, newsclips (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Yearbook, ca. 1944 (Box 10)
    - Yearbook, U.S. Army Training Center Engineer, Ft. Leonard Wood, MO, 26 Oct. 1961 (Box 10)
  - WWII research materials
    - WW II uniform insignia (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Michael J. Maher promotion leave papers, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Island of Oahu map, photos, newslips, WWII (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Kilauea Military Camp, HI, images, WWII (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Coastal defenses, Sabine Pass, Freeport, WWII (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Fred S. Hartman (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Major Maurice Westerfield enlistment/discharge papers, WWII (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - USS Houston enlistment ceremony anniversary, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - USS Houston enlistment ceremony sale items (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Visit of USS Houston to city, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Price family materials (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 12)